Kevin Espinoza

Contact

in

LinkedIn Kevin Espinoza

<u>KevinEspinozaDev</u>

M

kevinespinozadev@gmail.com



+54 2995476575



Rio Negro, Argentina

Main Technologies



Angular



TypeScript



Material



Bootstrap

Other Technologies



Ionic



React JS



Postman



Jira Software - SCRUM





GIT and GitHub

Soft Skills

- Responsibility
- Teamwork
- Investigation
- Organization
- Detailed
- High interest in international projects

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

About Me

I am a Web Developer with Full-Stack training at the National University of Comahue. I seek to develop myself professionally in the Front-End. I like technology, music, video games and I value camaraderie and empathy. When I write code, I always do it user-oriented so that the user has the best experience.

Work Experience

ANGULAR DEVELOPER

Latamcode Jul 2021 - At present

- Development of the education management system of the Province of Neuquén, Argentina
- Front-End Development with Angular and Angular Material
- Integration with RESTful APIs
- Agile SCRUM methodology and use of Jira Software
- Unit and functional testing with Postman

PHP FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Blistersoft Oct 2020 - Jan 2021

- Development of statistical systems for oil companies
- Full-Stack Development with Codeigniter
- Front-End Layout with Bootstrap

PHP FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Extension project - National University of Comahue May 2020 - Aug 2020

- Development of event management platform "Juntar"
- Full Stack PHP development with Yii2
- Front-End Layout with Bootstrap
- Email design

Education

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF COMAHUE (ARG) Universitarian Associate Degree in Web Development | 2018 - 2021

COURSES, CERTIFICATIONS AND LANGUAGES

- UDEMY Laravel, API RESTful, Angular and Postman course | Jun 2021 - (See Certificate)
- ENGLISH: B2 Upper Intermediate (See Certificate)